A Guide to the William J. “Bill” Elvin Collection, 1914-2004, bulk 1963-2003
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 3: Photographs, 1956-2003
  - Boone, W.S., Jr. - with Mr. and Mrs. Lloyd Johnson, Undated (Box 28)
  - Boy Scouts - Derek Sneds, Peter Hesse, Max Padon, Sean Smolenyak, Undated (Box 28)
  - Braddock, Edward - Grave at Fort Necessity National Battlefield, Undated (Box 28)
  - Brewer, Judy, Undated (Box 28)
  - Broyhill, Joel T., 1993 (Box 28)
  - Brunswick, Maryland (negatives), 1991 (Box 28)
  - Brunswick, Maryland - Old B&O Roundhouse, 1993 (Box 28)
  - Brunswick, Maryland - Railroad Station, 1993 (Box 28)
  - Brunswick, Maryland - Steadman-Keenan American Legion Post 96, 1993 (Box 28)
  - Burke, Arleigh with Barbara Bush, Undated (Box 28)
  - Burling Tract, Undated (Box 28)
  - Burling Tract - with A. Linwood Holton and William S. Hoofnagle, 1991-2001 (Box 28)
  - Callahan, Vincent and Dorothy, c. 1958 (Box 28)
  - Carper Shopping Center Fire, 1997 December 2 (Box 28)
  - Chesterbrook Pumping Station, Undated (Box 28)
  - Chesterbrook United Methodist Church, Undated (Box 28)
  - CIA Child Care Center, 1993 March 14 (Box 28)
  - Commons of McLean, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Conrad, Suzanne H. Paciulli, Undated (Box 28)
  - Cooper Middle School - Denise Grant, Courtney May, Edmond Wybaillie, Jason Semales, Margo Elsayd, John Michael Fallon, Undated (Box 28)
  - Covanta Waste Energy Plant, Undated (Box 28)
  - Cub Scouts, Undated (Box 28)
  - D-Day Normandy Landings, 1993 (Box 28)
  - Davis, Mary Singer, Undated (Box 28)
  - DeCorpo, Susan, 1988 November (Box 28)
  - Dinsmore, Linda with Secretary William E. Simon, 1977 (Box 28)
  - DuBose, Bill - with Emory Hackman and Bobbie Hebert, Undated (Box 28)
  - Elvin, Bill, Undated (Box 28)
  - Elvin, Bill - Home at 901 Mackall Avenue, 1956 November (Box 28)
  - Elvin, Bill - Retirement Party, Undated (Box 28)
  - Elvin, Bill - with John F. Herrity and Joan DuBois, 1979 (Box 28)
  - Elvin, Bill - with Stu Mendelson, 2000 (Box 28)
  - Epperson, Duane, Undated (Box 28)
  - Evans Farm Inn, Undated (Box 28)
  - Fairfax County Recycling Center, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Fantasy Baseball, Undated (Box 28)
  - Forestville Schoolhouse, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Fred Lilly House, Undated (Box 28)
  - Frey, Michael, 1997 December 6 (Box 28)
  - Gabeler, Lane R., 2003 (Box 28)
  - Gasch, Manning, 1993 (Box 28)
  - Gott, John K. - with William L. White, Mrs. Walter Sheeler and W. Everett Triplett, Undated (Box 28)
  - Great Falls, 1961-1995 (Box 28)
  - Gregory, Anne Morton, 2000 (Box 28)
  - Griffith, Elisabeth, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hayzlett, Rev. Woodrow W., 1966 (Box 28)
  - Hazleton Laboratories, 1968 (Box 28)
  - Hickory Hill, 1990 June 9 (Box 28)
  - Hicks, George D., Jr., Undated (Box 28)
  - Higgins, George L., Undated (Box 28)
  - Higgins, Stephen E., Undated (Box 28)
  - High, Martha W., 1990 August 19 (Box 28)
  - Hill, Mrs. Wellman A., Undated (Box 28)
  - Hill, Wanda, 1989 July 13 (Box 28)
  - Hill, Wayne K., Jr., 1986 (Box 28)
  - Hinds, Max, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hinds, Mrs. Max K., Undated (Box 28)
  - Hinkel, Donald J., 1981 (Box 28)
  - Hinkle, Dr. Alan, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hinkle, Richard R., Undated (Box 28)
  - Hirst, Jessica Fairfax, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hirst, Omer L., Undated (Box 28)
  - Hirst, Thomson M., Undated (Box 28)
  - Hobson, Richard, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hobson, Richard W., Undated (Box 28)
  - Hodgson, Aldred S., Undated (Box 28)
  - Hofer, Florian N., Undated (Box 28)
  - Holbein, Mary Elizabeth, Undated (Box 28)
  - Holbrook, Frank, 1984 (Box 28)
  - Holland, Franklin S., Jr., 1987 (Box 28)
  - Holland, Harold H., Undated (Box 28)
  - Holley, Estelle R., 1988 (Box 28)
  - Holmberg, Susan Lee, Undated (Box 28)
  - Holmes, Lawrence L., 1987 (Box 28)
  - Holmes, Marjorie, Undated (Box 28)
  - Holroyd, Mrs. L.J., Undated (Box 28)
  - Holt, Barry, Undated (Box 28)
  - Holt, Joseph, Undated (Box 28)
  - Holton, Dwight, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Holton, Jinks, Undated (Box 28)
  - Holton, Linwood, Undated (Box 28)
  - Home Detention Bracelet, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hood, Lorena, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hoofnagle, Jim, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hoofnagle, William S., Undated (Box 28)
  - Hooker, Robinetta, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hooper, Mary Elizabeth, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hoopes, Townsend, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hopkins, Gerald, Undated (Box 28)
  - Horahan, Rebecca Joy, Undated (Box 28)
  - Horan, Robert F. Jr, 1972-1993 (Box 28)
  - Horowitz, B. M., Undated (Box 28)
  - Horowitz, Barry M., 1987 (Box 28)
  - Horse, Undated (Box 28)
  - Horse Shoe Drive - Controlled Fire, 1993 (Box 28)
  - Horton, John F., 1985 (Box 28)
  - Horton, Patricia, Undated (Box 28)
  - Horvath, Steve, Undated (Box 28)
  - Horwatt, David, Undated (Box 28)
  - Horwatt, Michael S., 1986 (Box 28)
  - Hougen, H. Monty, 1984 (Box 28)
  - Howard, Herman A., 1986 (Box 28)
  - Howell, Janet D., 1991 (Box 28)
  - Howlett, Myles R., Undated (Box 28)
  - Howlett, William C., Undated (Box 28)
  - Hsia, Jin-Sung, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hsia, Juddith Ann, 1987 (Box 28)
  - Hubbard, Karetta, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hubbard, Stephen J., 1990 (Box 28)
  - Hubbard, Tony Ditto, Undated (Box 28)
  - Huber, Maya, Undated (Box 28)
  - Huckaby, Susan, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hudson, William, 1986 (Box 28)
  - Huebner, Dr. Gilbert D., Undated (Box 28)
  - Huff, Roger A., Undated (Box 28)
  - Huge, Harry, Undated (Box 28)
  - Huggins, M. Wayne, 1985-1987 (Box 28)
  - Hughes, James C., Undated (Box 28)
  - Hunt, Donnie, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hunter, Marilyn, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hunting Ridge construction, 1997 December 18 (Box 28)
  - Hurwitch, Robert, Undated (Box 28)
  - Huston, Paul, Undated (Box 28)
  - Hvozdovic, Joanie, 1994 September 30 (Box 28)
  - Hwang, Gloria, 1987 November 19 (Box 28)
  - Hyatt, Ronald I., Undated (Box 28)
  - Hynes, Martha Soyster, Undated (Box 28)
  - Icicles on McLean building, Undated (Box 28)
  - Ingleside, Undated (Box 28)
  - Jackson, Dr. Charles, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Jackson, Francis J., Undated (Box 28)
  - Jackson, Mary V., Undated (Box 28)
  - Jackson, Rev. Thomas A., 1988 (Box 28)
  - Jackson, Timothy E., 1986 (Box 28)
  - Jackson, William P., Jr., 1978 (Box 28)
  - Jacobi, Thomas, Undated (Box 28)
  - Jacobs, Bill, Undated (Box 28)
  - Jaeger, Carl C., Undated (Box 28)
  - Jaffa, Elliott, Undated (Box 28)
  - Jamborsky, Richard J., 1990 (Box 28)
  - Jauchem, C.R., Undated (Box 28)
  - Jellama, Dave, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Jenkins, David M., 1987 (Box 28)
  - Jenkins, Web, Undated (Box 28)
  - Jennings, Barnard F., 1989 (Box 28)
  - Jernigan, Sam A., 1983 (Box 28)
  - Jeter, Timothy R., Undated (Box 28)
  - Jobe, Milton L., Undated (Box 28)
  - Joggerst, Margaret Wyatt, Undated (Box 28)
  - Johns, Homer, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Johnson, Donna, Undated (Box 28)
  - Johnson, Dr. George, Undated (Box 28)
  - Johnson, George W., 1978-1992 (Box 28)
  - Johnson, Henry E., Undated (Box 28)
  - Johnson, Leon W., Undated (Box 28)
  - Johnson, Nels E., Undated (Box 28)
  - Johnson, Rady A., 1986 (Box 28)
  - Johnson, Robert E., Undated (Box 28)
  - Johnson, Robert M., 1987-1988 (Box 28)
  - Johnson, Walter P., Undated (Box 28)
  - Jones, Betty, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Jones, Billy, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Jones, Compton S., Undated (Box 28)
  - Jones, Dr. Robert G., Undated (Box 28)
  - Jones, Shirley E., Undated (Box 28)
  - Jones, Stanley R., 1985 (Box 28)
  - Jones, Timothy W., 1981 (Box 28)
  - Jordan, George S., Undated (Box 28)
  - Jordan, Mary, 1984 (Box 28)
  - Journal Building, 1987 (Box 28)
  - Journal Building [mounted photographs], Undated (Box 28)
  - Joyal, Cheryl Lynn, Undated (Box 28)
  - Joyce, Dana - with Tom and Chad Joyce, Undated (Box 28)
  - Juergens, Richard K., Jr., 1986 (Box 28)
  - Just Say No Drug Class, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kalaris, Themis, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kalmus, Sheldon, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kaln, Deborah, 1985 (Box 28)
  - Kane, Jeanne, 1987 (Box 28)
  - Kane, Mark, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Kane, Patrick F., 1990 (Box 28)
  - Kaplan, Debbie, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kaplan, Martin and Laura, Undated (Box 28)
  - Karabatsos, Kimon T., 1976 (Box 28)
  - Karmol, Colleen, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Karsner, Loran P., Undated (Box 28)
  - Karsten, Jayne, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kaul Building - Baskin Robbins Ice Cream and Dominion Hardware, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kautz, Lynford E., 1985 (Box 28)
  - Kaye, Dean S., Undated (Box 28)
  - Keane, James M., Undated (Box 28)
  - Keating, Bishop John R., 1984 (Box 28)
  - Keating, Joseph A., Undated (Box 28)
  - Keenan, Barbara, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Keenan, Kathleen, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Keene, Chef Anthony - Tysons Ritz-Carlton opening, 1991 November 6 (Box 28)
  - Keever, Robert, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kegley, Milt, Undated (Box 28)
  - Keith, Donald E., Undated (Box 28)
  - Keith, James, Undated (Box 28)
  - Keker, Samuel J., 1991 (Box 28)
  - Keliher, Michael J., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kellar, Arthur, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kelley, Michael, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kelly, H. Wise, Jr., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kelly, Harold V., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kelly, Paul A., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kemp, Jack - with John Herrity and David G. Sanders, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Kendrick, Caldwell C., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kennedy, Anthony M. - House at 6819 Wemberly Way, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kennedy, Edward M. - House at 634 Chain Bridge Road, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kennedy, Ehtel - with Birch Bayh, John Flannery, and Bettina Gregory, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kennedy, Gary D., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kennedy, James D., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kennedy, Karen, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kennedy, Mrs. Cornelius B., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kennedy, Robert F., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kent, Denton W., 1982 (Box 28)
  - Kerlin, Julie O., Undated (Box 28)
  - Keyworth, George A., II, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kier, Jane Lulu, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kilberg, Bobbie, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Kildee, Dale E., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kilfeather, Dr. John E., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kimball, John, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kimble, Mason, 1964 (Box 28)
  - King, Donald H., Undated (Box 28)
  - King, Dr. David, 1982 (Box 28)
  - King, Edward G., Jr., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kingdon, William R., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kings Manor sign, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kinnear, George E.R., II, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kinney, David B., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kirby Road and Old Dominion Drive, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kirkbride, Gary W., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kissman, Katha, Undated (Box 28)
  - Kline, John D., Undated (Box 28)
  - Klopfenstein, Peyton, Undated (Box 28)
  - Klose, Thomas J., 1986 (Box 28)
  - Knapp, Dr. W.A., Jr., Undated (Box 28)
  - Knight, Kerry J., Undated (Box 28)
  - Knoblauch, H.C., Undated (Box 28)
  - Kuriyama, Masako, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lake Fairfax, 1993 (Box 28)
  - Langan, Thomas P., Undated (Box 28)
  - Langley Fork, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Langley Fork - Historical Marker Dedication, 1996 (Box 28)
  - Langley High School Sports, Undated (Box 28)
  - Laughlin Inc. Realtor Building, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lefton, Dr. Charles, Undated (Box 28)
  - Leigh, A. Claiborne, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lewinsville Water Tank, 1997 December 2 (Box 28)
  - Lichtman, Judith, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lieurance, N.A., Undated (Box 28)
  - Lillard, Betty E., Undated (Box 28)
  - Lilly, George, 1988-2000 (Box 28)
  - Lindberg, Carolyn, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lindholm, William L., Undated (Box 28)
  - Lindsey, Harry, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lintz, Mary Grace, Undated (Box 28)
  - Linway Terrace and Old Dominion Drive, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lion, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lipsey, Geoffrey W., Undated (Box 28)
  - Litovitz, Dr. Gary, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Litton, Andrew, Undated (Box 28)
  - Loomis, Henry, Undated (Box 28)
  - Loughborough, Larry, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Loughery, Richard M., Undated (Box 28)
  - Loughran, David W., 1988 (Box 28)
  - Loux, Gordon D., 1987 (Box 28)
  - Love, Jack, Undated (Box 28)
  - Love, Rita, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lovejoy, Thomas E., 1987 (Box 28)
  - Lovelace, Bob, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lovey, Pat, Undated (Box 28)
  - Loving, William H., Undated (Box 28)
  - Low, James P., Undated (Box 28)
  - Lowe, Elward W., Undated (Box 28)
  - Lowe, Julian C., Undated (Box 28)
  - Lowrey, Dr. Charles W., Undated (Box 28)
  - Lowstuter, Anthony R., Jr., 1986 (Box 28)
  - LSD, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lucas, Grace, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lucas, Robert W., Undated (Box 28)
  - Lucci, Susan, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lucien, David C., Undated (Box 28)
  - Ludwig, John M., Undated (Box 28)
  - Luedtke, Glenn, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lugenbeel, Irene, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lukens, Judy, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lundgren, Mary Ann, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lundquist, Donald E., Undated (Box 28)
  - Lundy, Robert F., 1975 (Box 28)
  - Lunger, W. Pless, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lutkins, Nick, 1989 (Box 28)
  - Lutz, Conrad, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lyman, Julia Parker, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Lynch, Frank - Frank Lynch Tires, Undated (Box 28)
  - Lynn, Orville B., Undated (Box 28)
  - MacDonald, Alan R., 1975 (Box 28)
  - MacDonald, Dr. Gordon J.F., Undated (Box 28)
  - MacFarland, Harold N., Undated (Box 28)
  - Mack, Donna, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Mackall, Mrs. Douglass S., III, Undated (Box 28)
  - Mackin, Derril, Undated (Box 28)
  - MacLane, Kathryn Ann, Undated (Box 28)
  - Macy, John W., Jr., Undated (Box 28)
  - Macy's, Undated (Box 28)
  - Madison Building, Undated (Box 28)
  - Madison National Bank, Undated (Box 28)
  - Maffitt, Rev. William (grave), Undated (Box 28)
  - Magness, William H., Undated (Box 28)
  - Mahaffie, Jane, Undated (Box 28)
  - Maher, James, Undated (Box 28)
  - Mahoney, Thomas, Undated (Box 28)
  - Mahoney, W. Scott, Undated (Box 28)
  - Maichak, Thomas H., Undated (Box 28)
  - Mainland, Ed, Undated (Box 28)
  - Malek, Frederic V., Undated (Box 28)
  - Mallison, Linda A., Undated (Box 28)
  - Malone, Thomas K., 1984 (Box 28)
  - Manger, Thomas, 1991 (Box 28)
  - Manges, Catherine, 1984 (Box 28)
  - Mann, Charles - House at 11385 Seneca Knoll Drive, Undated (Box 28)
  - Mann, Judy, Undated (Box 28)
  - Manning, Jay, Undated (Box 28)
  - Manson, Charles T., Undated (Box 28)
  - Maplewood, Undated (Box 28)
  - Marchant, Larry, Undated (Box 28)
  - Margolis, Eugene, 1987 (Box 28)
  - Mariella, Raymond P., Undated (Box 28)
  - Marik, Robert, 1987 (Box 28)
  - Markel, Howard B., Undated (Box 28)
  - Markley, Carroll C., Undated (Box 28)
  - Marks, Tracy, Undated (Box 28)
  - Marlin-Jones, Davey, Undated (Box 28)
  - Marran, Jay, Undated (Box 28)
  - Marriott - Tysons Corner, Undated (Box 28)
  - Mars, Virginia, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Marsh, Gen. Robert T., 1985 (Box 28)
  - Marsh, Hugh B., Undated (Box 28)
  - Marsh, Jo, Undated (Box 28)
  - Marshall, Conrad, Undated (Box 28)
  - Marshall, George C. - Statue in Leesburg, Undated (Box 28)
  - Marshall, Richard C., Undated (Box 28)
  - Marshall, Virginia C., 1989 (Box 28)
  - Martin, C. Joseph, Undated (Box 28)
  - Martin, Dr. Dean, Undated (Box 28)
  - Martin, Lawrence, Undated (Box 28)
  - Martin, Mervyn M., Undated (Box 28)
  - Martyak, Vicki F., Undated (Box 28)
  - Marvil, Patricia Del, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Mason, George (stamp), Undated (Box 29)
  - Mason, Richard S., Undated (Box 29)
  - Mason, William F., 1987 (Box 29)
  - Mason, William L., 1988 (Box 29)
  - Massa, Cliff, Undated (Box 29)
  - Massell, Richard C., Undated (Box 29)
  - Massey Building, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Mathews, Mrs. David, Undated (Box 29)
  - Mathison, Donald, Undated (Box 29)
  - Matisoff, Nancy, 1984 (Box 29)
  - Matney, Joseph S., Undated (Box 29)
  - Mattson, Alexandra, 1990 (Box 29)
  - May, Jane, Undated (Box 29)
  - Mayo, Claude "Bud", Undated (Box 29)
  - McArver, R. Dennis, Undated (Box 29)
  - McBride, Robert, Undated (Box 29)
  - McCaffrey, Joseph P., 1981 (Box 29)
  - McCall, Chester H., Sr., Undated (Box 29)
  - McCandlish, Mary L., 1972 (Box 29)
  - McCann, Betty, Undated (Box 29)
  - McCarthy, Leah, Undated (Box 29)
  - McClanahan, Robert M., Undated (Box 29)
  - McClanahan, Walter B., Undated (Box 29)
  - McClean, Marsha, Undated (Box 29)
  - McClelland, Anne H., 1978 (Box 29)
  - McCloskey, Frances McAllister, 1985 (Box 29)
  - McCloskey, Mary Catherine, 1986 (Box 29)
  - McCloskey, Peter F., Undated (Box 29)
  - McConahy, Robert L., 2003 (Box 29)
  - McCormick, Susan, Undated (Box 29)
  - McCracken, Deborah A., Undated (Box 29)
  - McCracken, Samuel J., Undated (Box 29)
  - McCrann, Duncan, Undated (Box 29)
  - McCulla, Pat, Undated (Box 29)
  - McDermott, Francis M., Undated (Box 29)
  - McDiarmid, Dorothy, 1987-1989 (Box 29)
  - McDonald, Clark E., Undated (Box 29)
  - McDonald, David, 1993 (Box 29)
  - McDonald, James P., Undated (Box 29)
  - McDonald, Joe, Undated (Box 29)
  - McDonald, Jonathan W., 1986 (Box 29)
  - McDonald's, Undated (Box 29)
  - McDonnell, Jane B., Undated (Box 29)
  - McDowell, Rob, 1995 May 6 (Box 29)
  - McGarvey, John A., 1984 (Box 29)
  - McGuire, Frank G., 1978 (Box 29)
  - McIlwee, James T., Jr., Undated (Box 29)
  - McInnis, Mary Ellen, Undated (Box 29)
  - McInnis, Ray, Undated (Box 29)
  - McIntosh, Robert F., Undated (Box 29)
  - McKnew, William C., 1987 (Box 29)
  - McLaughlin, Edward "Ted" - with Mary and Ted McLaughlin, Undated (Box 29)
  - McLean Animal Hospital, 1988 July 5 (Box 29)
  - McLean Arts Center, Undated (Box 29)
  - McLean Bible Church, Undated (Box 29)
  - McLean Community Center, Undated (Box 29)
  - McLean Farmers Market, Undated (Box 29)
  - McLean Flower Affair - Diane Lacosey Mowry, 1989 (Box 29)
  - McLean Hardware - Mike Cannon, 1989 (Box 29)
  - McLean High School, Undated (Box 29)
  - McLean Hilton - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors, Undated (Box 29)
  - McLean Hilton at Tysons Corner - C. Arnie Quirion, Kim Farmer, and Michelle McCalla, Undated (Box 29)
  - McLean House Condominium, Undated (Box 29)
  - McLean Little League, 1991 (Box 29)
  - McLean Medical Center Pharmacy, Undated (Box 29)
  - McLean Mews, Undated (Box 29)
  - McLean Orchestra, 1994 April 9 (Box 29)
  - McLean Post Office, 1970-1989 (Box 29)
  - McLean Post Office - West McLean Branch, 1984 (Box 29)
  - McLean Presbyerian Church, 1989 December 24 (Box 29)
  - McLean Project for the Arts, 1986 (Box 29)
  - McLean Project for the Arts - Vincent F. Callahan Jr., Evelyn Swindler, Nancy Weyl, Lilla Richards, William J. Elvin, John S. Hannon Jr., Undated (Box 29)
  - McLean Safe Deposit, 1989 July 29 (Box 29)
  - McLean Savings, Undated (Box 29)
  - McLean Shopping Center - Giant Food, 1989 (Box 29)
  - McLean Square Mall, 1972-1989 (Box 29)
  - McLean streetviews, 1985 April (Box 29)
  - McLean Trees Foundation recycling bin, Undated (Box 29)
  - McLean Virginia Stake of The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints, 1987 (Box 29)
  - McLean Volunteer Fire Department, 1975-1988 (Box 29)
  - McLean, Elliott G., Undated (Box 29)
  - McLucas, John L., 1985 (Box 29)
  - McMahon, Charles D. - with Harry L. Carrico and William C. Wooldridge, Undated (Box 29)
  - McMahon, Linda, Undated (Box 29)
  - McMahon, Toni Winters, 1984 (Box 29)
  - McNamara, Geoffrey, Undated (Box 29)
  - McNerney, Margaret, Undated (Box 29)
  - McNulty, Peggy, Undated (Box 29)
  - McReery, Bailey, Undated (Box 29)
  - McVay, Wyatt C., 1986 (Box 29)
  - McVicker, H. Keith, Undated (Box 29)
  - Medich, William, Undated (Box 29)
  - Meehan, John J., Undated (Box 29)
  - Meeker, Bob, Undated (Box 29)
  - Meese, Dana Lynne, Undated (Box 29)
  - Meese, Michael J., 1981 (Box 29)
  - Meese, Ursula, Undated (Box 29)
  - Meetze, Henry W., 1976 (Box 29)
  - Megill, Douglas B., Undated (Box 29)
  - Mehle, Roger W., Undated (Box 29)
  - Melancon, Cheryl Ann, Undated (Box 29)
  - Melin, Gina, 1984 (Box 29)
  - Mendelson, Stu, 1995 May 6 (Box 29)
  - Mense, Lewis H. "Hank", 1973 (Box 29)
  - Merkle, Theodore J., Jr., Undated (Box 29)
  - Merriman, Ronald, 1984 (Box 29)
  - Merrywood, Undated (Box 29)
  - Mesmeralda's, Undated (Box 29)
  - Metcalf, Eric, Undated (Box 29)
  - Metcalf, Joseph, III, Undated (Box 29)
  - Methven, Alex, Undated (Box 29)
  - Methvin, Claudia, 1989 (Box 29)
  - Metro, Undated (Box 29)
  - Metzger, Evelyn, Undated (Box 29)
  - Meyer, A. Phoebe, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Middendorf, J. William, II, Undated (Box 29)
  - Miklich, Joey, Undated (Box 29)
  - Milks, John, 1983 (Box 29)
  - Miller and Smith Offices - 1301 Beverly Road, Undated (Box 29)
  - Miller, Andrew P., Undated (Box 29)
  - Miller, David H., Undated (Box 29)
  - Miller, Doris Brown, Undated (Box 29)
  - Miller, Frances J., 1985 (Box 29)
  - Miller, Harold O., Undated (Box 29)
  - Miller, Harris, 1984 (Box 29)
  - Miller, James C., Undated (Box 29)
  - Miller, Joanna, Undated (Box 29)
  - Miller, Linda H., 1985 (Box 29)
  - Miller, Renee, Undated (Box 29)
  - Miller, Robert F., 1987 (Box 29)
  - Miller, William A., Undated (Box 29)
  - Millett, William J., Undated (Box 29)
  - Mills, John A., Undated (Box 29)
  - Miniclier, Kit, Undated (Box 29)
  - Mitchell, Carol, Undated (Box 29)
  - Mitchell, Perry, Undated (Box 29)
  - Mitchell, Robert, Undated (Box 29)
  - Mitchell, Roy S., Undated (Box 29)
  - Mitre Corporation, Undated (Box 29)
  - Mittelman, Frederick S., 2003 (Box 29)
  - Mohr, Catherine A., Undated (Box 29)
  - Mollison, Char, Undated (Box 29)
  - Molo, William, Undated (Box 29)
  - Monahan, Jayne, 1986 (Box 29)
  - Money, Jim, Undated (Box 29)
  - Monk, Art, Undated (Box 29)
  - Montague, Robert L., III, Undated (Box 29)
  - Montgomery, Barbara Dill, Undated (Box 29)
  - Moon, Sun Myung, Undated (Box 29)
  - Moore Cadillac, Undated (Box 29)
  - Moore, Ann, 1983 (Box 29)
  - Moore, Audrey, 1987-1991 (Box 29)
  - Moore, Charles A., Jr., 1985 (Box 29)
  - Moore, Frances, 1986 (Box 29)
  - Moore, Mark D., Undated (Box 29)
  - Moore, Richard M., 1987 (Box 29)
  - Moore, Sharon Dee, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Moore, Thaddeus T., 1983 (Box 29)
  - Moorer, Adm. Thomas, Undated (Box 29)
  - Morabite residence - 1133 Chain Bridge Road, Undated (Box 29)
  - Moran, James P. "Jim", 1991-1992 (Box 29)
  - Moreau, Col. Jean W., Undated (Box 29)
  - Morganstern, Barbara, Undated (Box 29)
  - Morgenstern, Oscar L., 1983 (Box 29)
  - Morris, Cherie, Undated (Box 29)
  - Morris, Jim, Undated (Box 29)
  - Morris, Martin E., Undated (Box 29)
  - Morris, S. Barry, Undated (Box 29)
  - Morrison, Capt. Quinn B., Undated (Box 29)
  - Morrison, Jean A., 1985 (Box 29)
  - Morrison, Jim, 1984 (Box 29)
  - Morrison, Timothy M., 1991 (Box 29)
  - Morrissette, Mrs. John, Undated (Box 29)
  - Moskal, LilyB, Undated (Box 29)
  - Mount, H. Paul, Undated (Box 29)
  - Mudd, Roger H., 1988 (Box 29)
  - Mueller, Judith, Undated (Box 29)
  - Mug Shots, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Mulligan, Dr. Louis T., 1984 (Box 29)
  - Mullins, D. Patrick, Undated (Box 29)
  - Mullins, Russell, Undated (Box 29)
  - Murphy, Mary Meade, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Murphy, Peter F., Jr., 1991 (Box 29)
  - Murphy, Walter F., 1981 (Box 29)
  - Murray, William W., 1975 (Box 29)
  - Mutersbaugh, Cline, Undated (Box 29)
  - Myer, Paul J., 1988 (Box 29)
  - Myers, Larry, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Myers, Rev. Mary R., Undated (Box 29)
  - Myers, Rev. William F., 1982 (Box 29)
  - Myles, Eve, 1983 (Box 29)
  - Nakache, Patricia, Undated (Box 29)
  - Nathan, Tink, Undated (Box 29)
  - Nation, Chris, Undated (Box 29)
  - Nay, Robert E., 1987 (Box 29)
  - Naylor, Mrs. William E., Jr., Undated (Box 29)
  - Nealson, James D., Undated (Box 29)
  - Neiman Marcus, Undated (Box 29)
  - Nelson, Karl R., 1986 (Box 29)
  - Nelson, Verl, Undated (Box 29)
  - Nelson's Chapel Methodist Church (site of), Undated (Box 29)
  - Netwig, John, Undated (Box 29)
  - Neuman, Pat, Undated (Box 29)
  - Neviaser, Charles M., Undated (Box 29)
  - Newbill, Robert A., 1987 (Box 29)
  - Newcomb, Lamar A., Undated (Box 29)
  - Newcombe, Jim, Undated (Box 29)
  - Newcome, Wayne, Undated (Box 29)
  - Newman, Cynthia, Undated (Box 29)
  - Newman, Col. Paul A., Undated (Box 29)
  - Newman, Robert C., 1989 (Box 29)
  - Neyhart, Robert J., Undated (Box 29)
  - Nichols, Mrs. William, Undated (Box 29)
  - Nichols, Dr. Robert S., 1982 (Box 29)
  - Nichols, Thomas, 1985 (Box 29)